
let questions3 = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which is the national sport of Canada?",
    answer: "Lacrosse/Ice hockey",
    options: [
      "Lacrosse/Ice hockey",
      "Cricket",
      "Field hockey",
      "Volleyball"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Archery is the national sport of which country?",
    answer: "Bhutan",
    options: [
      "Afghanistan",
      "Bhutan",
      "Japan",
      "India"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Among these which country has Cricket as its national sports",
    answer: "Jamaica",
    options: [
      "India",
      "Jamaica",
      "Sri Lanka",
      "United States"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which is the national sport of Turkey?",
    answer: "Wrestling",
    options: [
      "Wrestling",
      "Rugby union",
      "Golf",
      "Basketball"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "When was the Commonwealth game started?",
    answer: "1930",
    options: [
      "1934",
      "1938",
      "1930",
      "1950"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which country has won Cricket world cup for the maximum number of times?",
    answer: "Australia",
    options: [
      "Australia",
      "India",
      "West Indies",
      "Sri Lanka"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Football World Cup has been won by which country for the maximum number of times?",
    answer: "Brazil",
    options: [
      "Italy",
      "Uruguay",
      "West Germany",
      "Brazil"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which country has hosted Commonwealth Games for the maximum number of times?",
    answer: "Canada",
    options: [
      "Canada",
      "New Zealand",
      "England",
      "Scotland"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "First Olympic Games was held in",
    answer: "Canada",
    options: [
      "England",
      "Australia",
      "Jamacia",
      "Canada"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following awards is given for excellence in sports coaching in India?",
    answer: "Dronacharya Award",
    options: [
      "Arjuna Awards",
      "Dronacharya Award",
      "Dhyan Chand Award",
      "Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna"
    ]
  },

];